[
 {
    "question": "What is a correct syntax to output \"Hello World\" in C++?",
    "choices1": "cout<<\"Hello World\";",
    "choices2": "System.out.Println(\"Hello World\");",
    "choices3": "printf(\"Hello World\")",
    "choices4": "print(\"Hello World\")",
    "Answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the pure virtual function definition from the following.",
    "choices1" : " virtual void f()=0 { }",
    "choices2" : " void virtual f()=0 { }",
    "choices3" : "virtual void f() {} = 0;",
    "choices4" : " None of the above.",
    "Answer" : 4
  },

  {
    "question": "Choose the Object oriented programming language from below.",
    "choices1" : "C++",
    "choices2" : "small talk",
    "choices3" : "simula",
    "choices4" : "all of the above",
    "Answer" : 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature of the OOPS gives the concept of reusability?",
    "choices1" : "Abstraction",
    "choices2" : "Encapsulation",
    "choices3" : "Inheritance",
    "choices4" : "None of the above.",
    "Answer" : 3
  },
  {
    "question": "With respective to streams >> (operator) is called as",
    "choices1" : "Insertion operator",
    "choices2" : "Extraction operator",
    "choices3" : "Right shift operator",
    "choices4" : "Left shift operator",
    "Answer" : 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Following is the invalid inclusion of a file to the current program. Identify it",
    "choices1" : "#include <file>",
    "choices2" : "#include \"file\"",
    "choices3" : "#include < file",
    "choices4" : " All of the above are invalid",
    "Answer" : 3
  },
    {
    "question": "How many keywords in C++?",
    "choices1" : "34",
    "choices2" : "32",
    "choices3" : "64",
    "choices4" : "128",
    "Answer" : 2
  },

    {
    "question": "What is the syntax of overloading operator + for class A?",
    "choices1" : "A operator+(argument_list){}",
    "choices2" : "A operator[+](argument_list){}",
    "choices3" : "int +(argument_list){}",
    "choices4" : "int [+](argument_list){}",
    "Answer" : 1
    },
  {
    "question": " How many approaches are used for operator overloading?",
    "choices1" : "1",
    "choices2" : "2",
    "choices3" : "3",
    "choices4" : "4",
    "Answer" : 3
    },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statement is not true about preprocessor directives?\n",
    "choices1" : "These are lines read and processed by the preprocessor\n",
    "choices2" : "They do not produce any code by themselves",
    "choices3" : "These must be written on their own line",
    "choices4" : "They end with a semicolon",
    "Answer" : 4
    }
]